Welcome back after the break.
You must have known about two shares by now.
First is UP, second is SRf, there
is no trade on Hdalco and
you must have roughly understood the view point of Nifty Bank Nifty.
Bring two shares of covering.
One is REC and the other is Paytm.
Ruchit Bhai, please tell me quickly.
What to do in REC and what to do on Paytm
?   There are
no fresh trade setups.  But
if there are existing positions then it would be
advisable to hold.  There is a pullback move and
in a pullback move you can expect a range around 422 420 in the near term.   The
only thing is that the support for fresh buying is
quite far down, so the risk
reward ratio is not that favourable.
In existing positions, I would say you can
hold by placing a stop loss of Rs 384.   If it
comes around 418 420 then
book profit there in the stock.  Dimp was the
second stock we discussed?
Paytm Paytm Sir or Paytm or yes so
in Paytm I think the momentum here seems a bit positive.
So the previous swing high of
840 has also been crossed by this stock today.
So here you can make fresh purchase with stop loss of 820
for targets around 875.
Ok.  Point taken sir.
You have placed a call on both the shares and Jain, as you
know, you have full rights.  You
can swipe, you can drop.  If you
want, you can reverse the shares and
give them to us.  So you have complete freedom.
So whatever shares you are giving,
we are getting its stop loss target.
We have put all these shares in the trade category
and we will show their report card on
Tuesday because Monday is a
holiday.  So whatever work will be done today, we will
show you on Tuesday how the trades have been done in all these.
Ok?  Ok?  So you should be very
selective and do the trades as
you get them.  Now let me get
two bearish shares checked
by sir.
Sir, I have two shares.  First is Muthoot Finance,
it is being unwinded today and is
very short in fact and second is ICICI LBARD
sir please check both of them once.
ICICI LBAD & Muthu Finance The
setup in Muthu Finance is bearish.  Even in yesterday's session, the
fall that we saw after the news, there were a
lot of volumes in the cash segment
and we also saw a lot of long unwinding
because the stock
market had not corrected for a long time.
Now trading around the 200-day moving average.
But there is
no advice to do any bottom pushing here.  So I
think there can be some more brightness and continuity.
This could at least be a time-wise consolidation, if not price-wise.
So
2150 to 1950 is the range where we
feel the stock will remain slightly sideways.
So there is no fresh trade setup.  It is
not advisable to take any fresh trade in the stock.   You can
avoid it for now.  But yes if you have an issue with the
stock because the stock has fallen in the last two days.